Amadeus Folego Curriculum vitae

AMADEUS FOLEGO DA SILVA

Born in Mauá, SP, 23/12/1988 - Single Aurora St. 787, ap. 52, São Paulo - SP, 01209-001

CONTACT INFO Email: amadeusfolego@gmail.com Phone: 55 11 95237-1152

Github: @badosu Twitter: @badosu_

PROFILE Versatile professional, with experience developing for the web, using .Net and Ruby.

Interested in Math, Computer Science and *Hacking* in general. Has familiarity, and good learning skills, for concepts and technologies which are relevant for the web.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

10/2014 Presumé http://presume.com.br

Technical partner on Presumé: a platform for pre-interviewing candidates.

12/2013 - 10/2014 Stackbuilders http://stackbuilders.com

Web development consultancy company based on NY and various offices around

the world. Many different projects.

10/2013 - 12/2013 Hubbiz http://hubbiz.com

Business search engine built with JRuby and ElasticSearch.

05/2013 - 10/2013 Palpiteros http://palpiteros.com

A football social platform, built with Backbone, RoR and some other tools.

11/2012 - 04/2013 ClickARQ http://clickarq.com.br

Architecture crowdsourcing startup, where I worked as the only developer.

06/2012 - 12/2012 Codeminer42 http://codeminer42.com

Worked in several startup projects, with Ruby, Java and Python.

01/2012 - 05/2012 Boo-box http://boo-box.com

Technology company, in which I got touch with high scale systems.

06/2010 - 11/2011 Betboo http://betboo.com

Online gaming website, where I worked on projects related with expansion to other countries (Asia and Europe)

INTERESTING PROJECTS

• Yogurt http://github.com/badosu/yogurt

A bootstrap for minimal ruby web applications

• Coil http://github.com/badosu/coil

A static site engine in Elixir.

• **Binding of caller** http://rubydoc.info/gems/binding_of_caller/ Helped implement the JRuby and Rubinius versions.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

01/2010 (unfinished) B.Sc. Mathematics Universidade Federal do ABC

2006 B.Sc. Science and Technology Universidade Federal do ABC

Dynamic modelling of the Magnetic Hysteresis phenomenon
Available at (pt-br): http://www.scribd.com/doc/21709933

- Teaching Assistant
 - Multi-Variable Calculus.
 - · Vectorial and Tensorial Calculus.